

# **Gabriel Forero**

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

🖾 fpleo03@gmail.com 🤳 3158045060 👂 Cl. 8a #78-70 Bogotá Kenedy

### Perfil

I am a frontend developer passionate about web development, I currently use the React library for the development of web applications deploying them in a repository in the cloud like GitHub, I have a solid knowledge of HTML CSS, and JavaScript, and I have a conversational level of English (b1).

I currently have experience creating web applications independently, either for personal projects or for projects carried out on a freelance basis.

I am an assertive person to communicate and transmits what I want to communicate, currently all the knowledge that I have acquired I have learned in a self-taught, like reading official documentation, Platzi, online platforms, and a lot of practice, with the mentality of updating my knowledge and not stay in non-functional practices.

### Formation

Frontend Developer

ene 2020 - presente

Platzi

English (B1)

ene 2015 - ene 2018

Univerisdad nacional de Colombia, Bogota

Ingeniería

ago 2020 - presente

Universidad de America, Bogota

## Experience

### Frontend Developer

feb 2021 - jun 2021

Cliente Freelance

Project of movies using JavaScript in greater proportion, making calls to the API available on the web through Axios, along with tools for manipulating the dom.

#### Frontend Developer

feb 2022 - ago 2022

Personal Project

I developed my web portfolio mainly with HTML CSS and JavaScript, with different internal pages in which I show my experience and some projects in which I have worked with technologies such as React, and others in which I made calls to some API to modify the dom according to the data obtained.

### Contact

Sitio web

leopoldo983.github.io

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/gabrielleonardo-forero-perea-83644121a

Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

React

Git

Testing

Languages

Español

English

Hobbies

Learn